<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>James Yoon</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2018-08-17T11:42:00-07:00</updated><entry><title>First Post</title><link href="/first-post.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-08-17T11:42:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-08-17T11:42:00-07:00</updated><author><name>James Yoon</name></author><id>tag:None,2018-08-17:/first-post.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for coming on to this blog and be able to read some of my fabulous writing (You know what's up). All kidding aside, the reason I created this blog was first and foremost, to see if I can actually do it. Can I take an idea from …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for coming on to this blog and be able to read some of my fabulous writing (You know what's up). All kidding aside, the reason I created this blog was first and foremost, to see if I can actually do it. Can I take an idea from my head and actually bring it to reality? Am I all bark and no bite? Second, to improve my writing and communication skills. By writing on a consistent basis, can I really hone my writing ability? Last but not least, to provide some kind of value to you, the reader. By sharing some of my insights and experiences, I hope that you are able to gain and/or learn something that you never had before or at the very least, get some entertainment value out of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name's James Yoon and I'm a programmer and a lifelong student. I'm passionate about technology, personal development, learning, sports, anime, and Mexican food. I'll most likely write about tech stuff, specifically data science, machine learning and AI, but I'll also write about things I'm interested in. For example, online course reviews, movie/anime/book reviews, analyses about soccer games, etc. If that is something you're interested in, you've come to the right place. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I'm excited about this new journey I'm about to embark. As the Philadelphia 76ers keep saying, you gotta "Trust the Process." Anyways, take care until next time.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>